Contact

mne36325i@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jacktheisen (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Hard worker
Customer Service
Team Leadership

Jack Theisen

Actively Looking for Full Stack Frontend Positions | Full Stack Junior Web Developer | JavaScript | MySQL | Strong People Skills 55411

Summary

I believe there are so many things in this world that are yet to be done and so many new stories to be told. My goal in life is to capture those incredible moments and ensure they live on forever.

I am a web developer based in Minnesota, focused on advancing my career farther into the development field. I am currently attending a full stack course at the University of Minnesota, with the intention on graduating as a junior full stack web developer. I absolutely love people, I love working with them, being around them, and leading them. Coming from 5 years of customer service and management background I would say I have had a decent share of a variety of problems I needed to solve come my way.

Experience

Team Car Care Dba Jiffy Lube 3 years 9 months

Lead Customer Service Advisor August 2021 - Present (5 months) Minneapolis, Minnesota, United States

General Manager April 2018 - August 2021 (3 years 5 months)

Education

University of Minnesota

Certificate, Web Devolopment · (August 2021 - January 2022)

Robbinsdale Cooper Senior High School Business/Commerce, General (2015 - 2018)